{
  "type": "flashcards",
  "language_code": "ja",
  "data": [
    {
      "question": "おんぜん（な）",
      "answer": "safe, secure"
    },
    {
      "question": "いろいろ（な）",
      "answer": "various"
    },
    {
      "question": "おおきな",
      "answer": "big; large"
    },
    {
      "question": "おしゃべり（な）",
      "answer": "talkative"
    },
    {
      "question": "おしゃれ（な）",
      "answer": "trendy, fashionable"
    },
    {
      "question": "かんたん（な）",
      "answer": "simple, easy"
    },
    {
      "question": "きけん（な）",
      "answer": "dangerous"
    },
    {
      "question": "きらい（な）",
      "answer": "dislike"
    },
    {
      "question": "きれい（な）",
      "answer": "clean; neat; pretty; beautiful"
    },
    {
      "question": "くさい",
      "answer": "smell; stinky"
    },
    {
      "question": "げんき（な）",
      "answer": "healthy; energetic; lively"
    },
    {
      "question": "しおわせ（な）",
      "answer": "happy"
    },
    {
      "question": "しずか（な）",
      "answer": "quiet"
    },
    {
      "question": "シンプルな",
      "answer": "simple"
    },
    {
      "question": "じょうず（な）",
      "answer": "skillfull"
    },
    {
      "question": "しんせつ（な）",
      "answer": "kind"
    },
    {
      "question": "すき（な）",
      "answer": "like"
    },
    {
      "question": "すてき（な）",
      "answer": "attractive; nice"
    },
    {
      "question": "だいじ（な）",
      "answer": "important; valuable"
    },
    {
      "question": "たいせつ（な）",
      "answer": "important; valuable; precious"
    }
  ]
}
